*music* Knew he was a killer First time that I saw him
Wonder how many girls he had left and left haunted But if he's a ghost then I can be a phantom Holding him for ransom Some, some, some boys are trying too hard He don't try at all though
Younger than my exes but he act like such a man so So I see nothing better, I keep him forever like a vendetta I, I, I see how this is gonna go Touch me and you'll never be alone
Island breeze and lights down low, no one has to know In the middle of the night, in my dreams You should see the things we do, baby
In the middle of the night, in my dreams I know I'm gonna be with you, so I take my time
Are you ready for it?
When I was a robber, first time that he saw me Stealing hearts and running off and never saying sorry
But if I'm a teason, he can join the heist, and we'll move to an island, and, and he can be my jailer, burden to this tailor.
Every love I've known in comparison is a failure.
I forget their names now, I'm so very tame now, never be the same now, now.
I, I, I see how this is gon' go. Touch me and you'll never be alone.
White island breeze and lights down low No one has to know In the middle of the night, in my dreams You should see the things we do, baby
In the middle of the night, in my dreams I know I'm gonna be with you so I take my time
Are you ready for it?
Baby, let the kids begin Let the kids begin Let the kids begin Baby, let the kids begin Let the kids begin Let the kids begin I, I, I see how this is gonna go
Touch me and you'll never be alone I, island, breeze and lights down low No one has to know In the middle of the night My dreams
You should see the things we do Baby In the middle of the night My dreams
I know I'm gonna be with you So take my time In the middle of the night Let the games begin Let the games begin Let the games begin
Are you ready for it?
Baby, let the games begin Let the games begin Let the games begin Are you ready for it?